Mochammad Ichsan

Jalan Kebon Anggrek, Cipete, Cilandak, 12410, Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

↓ +62 81291254795 • ☑ ichsanmochammad@gmail.com

www.ichsan1710.github.io/personal-portfolio • ♀ ichsan1710

About Me

Dedicated professional with over six years of experience in the hospitality industry. My journey has now led me to the exciting world of technology, where I am actively pursuing a career as a software developer. My background in hospitality has instilled in me adaptability and problem-solving skills. These skills have seamlessly translated into the technology sector, where I am eager to make a positive impact.

Languages

- Indonesian (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- German A2.1 (Basic)

Technical Skills

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, PostgreSQL
- o React.js, Three.js, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Redux, React Native

Education

Purwadhika Digital Technology Certificate in Bootcamp JC Full Stack Web Development	2023
Swiss German University Bachelor of Economics, Major in International Business	2016

Professional Experience

Mitra POS Lion Parcel Owner	Feb 2022 - Present
Fairmont Jakarta Front Office Supervisor	Jan 2020 - Dec 2021
Fairmont Jakarta Front Desk Agent	Feb 2017 - Jan 2020
Fairmont Jakarta Royal Service Agent	Sep 2016 - Feb 2017
Ayana Resort & Spa Bali Front Desk Agent	Sep 2014 - Sep 2015

Rimba Jimbaran Bali

Daily Worker Guest Service Jul 2014 - Aug 2014

Kunsportal Century Germany

Intern Marketing Apr 2013 - Aug 2013

Weatherford Indonesia

Intern Administration Sep 2011 - Jan 2012

Achievements

O Top Upseller: Dec 2014, Jan 2015, Aug 2018, Feb 2019, Apr 2020

- o Top Enrollment: Jan 2019, Feb 2019, Mar 2019, Jun 2019, Jul 2019, Aug 2019
- O Perfect Scores LQA Audit Q2 2019
- Employee of the month Fairmont Jakarta Oct 2019